B1 Daniel is listening to a talk on how to stay safe in natural disasters.
Listen with him and complete the notes below.
Hello everybody, today I'd like to give you some advice on dealing with natural disasters.
If there's a flood, you should get to high ground and stay there.
Don't get close to or even walk through the water as it may wash you away.
If you are caught in a typhoon, you must quickly go inside the nearest building.
The strong winds can move cars and other big objects, so it is very dangerous to be outside.
When an earthquake happens, you should get outside as soon as possible.
However, if you can't, stay under a strong desk or table to protect yourself.
Don't stand near a window because you may get hurt.
That's all for today's talk.
I hope you know more about how to keep yourself safe and sound.